

# Dragan Batandjiovski

Digital Marketing Specialist

Jonche Murdjevski 12, Bitola, 7000, North Macedonia 0038978259247 · <u>draganbatandjiov@gmail.com</u>

Date / Place of birth 05.April.1989, Bitola

**Driving license** 

ΑВ

### **Skills**

Leadership Skills

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Ability to Work in a Team

Adaptability

Fast Learner

Ability to Multitask

Communication Skills

Social Media

Marketing Strategy

**SEO Copywriting** 

Wordpress

Facebook Ads

**SEO** 

Digital Marketing

**Email Marketing** 

Google Ads

## **Profile**

Highly motivated individual ,striving for improvement and complementing my knowledge.

Responsible, reliable, self-disciplined person with strong work ethic acquired through previous practical training and experience. Experienced Digital Marketing Manager with extensive experience building, maintaining, and running successful digital marketing campaigns, and projects in Google ads and meta business suite .Bringing forth a motivated attitude and a variety of powerful skills acquired in the Digital Marketing Academy of Brainster .

# **Employment History**

Bar Manager, Мезе Бар ТЕМА и кафе бар Шатор, Bitola

September 2014 - May 2016

running a food and drink business, a small food & drink bar exact

working as ambulance driver, SFERA INTERNATIONAL, Bitola

September 2020 — February 2021

I have started in SFERA as a volunteer and initially participated in Youth Projects supported by the ERASMUS+ program since 2016. My highly advanced English-speaking skills have been extremely beneficial to our organization — I mastered in Security, Criminology and finance control. After my volunteering position I started working as ambulance driver on a project named: "Health care for children with Cardio and Respiratory sensitivity in the Cross-Border area" reference number: CN1-SO1.2-SO023, funded by "Interreg IPA Cross-border Cooperation Programme Greece-North Macedonia 2014-2020" program where our organization is partner. On position a contract from 1ST of September 2020 until 28 of February 2021.

# **Education**

Certified Digital Marketer , www.brainster.co - Education Centre for IT skills , Skopje

April 2022 — November 2022

Successfully finished the Academy for Digital marketing at Brainster education center for IT skills.

Through my education I have worked on real projects & clients such as:

# English German Serbian Bulgarian Croatian

### **Hobbies**

Gardening ,Learning German ,Running ,Adaptive hiking ,Mountain climbing ,Sports shooting with various weapons, Cooking.... Content marketing for Yes for Less Points 10/10

Landing Page for "When in Krushevo" Points 10/10

Brand Strategy for http://scamperedu.mk/ Points 10/10

PR Strategy for "Mavrovo 365"

Google Ads campaign for "Brainster"

Social media marketing campaign for "Bellina"

Brainster's DIGITAL MARKETING ACADEMY consisted of the following modules:

Digital Marketing, marketing fundamentals, digital marketing strategy, lead generation, email automation, content marketing, google advertising, search engine optimization, social media marketing & advertising and digital PR.

Professional title: Master in Criminology, MIT University Faculty of Security, Criminology and Financial Control Department: Criminology ECTS: 120, Skopje

September 2014 - August 2016

all the exams of the study program with Grade Point Average of 8,93 and 120 ECTS and was awarded the title Master of criminology where on 31.08.2016 successfully defended his master thesis.

Professional title: Graduate detective, First private university FON Skopje ECTS 180 credits Faculty of Detectives and Security Skopje University Studies in Security Sciences, Skopje

September 2008 - May 2013

Certificate of tactics in natural conditions summer camp (May 2010)

Certificate of tactics in natural conditions winter camp (March 2011)

Certificate of tactics in natural conditions winter camp 2nd place in skiing men Discipline: slalom

(March

### Practical classes:

07.07.2009 - 17.07.2009 Certificate for

performed practical training for students at the Police

station of general competence in the SIA Bitola

Area: protection of property and personal security of citizens

05.07.2010 -15.07.2010 Certificate for practical practical training for students at the police

station SIA Bitola

Area: public order and peace, general criminality

high school diploma, Highschool "Josip Broz Tito" Bitola Secondary Municipal school Josip Broz Tito, educational profile Social humanistic area, combination A, Bitola

October 2004 - October 2008

### Courses

Зајакнување и вмрежување на неет млади, SFERA INTERNATIONAL September 2022 — September 2022

Certificate In German Language, Goethe Institute Skopje

September 2020 — September 2021

Security License for people and property , Chamber of the Republic of North Macedonia for private security

September 2011 — September 2011

☐ Certificate of tactics in natural conditions winter camp ☐ Certificate of tactics in natural conditions winter camp 2nd place in skiing men Discipline: slalom, FON university with ARM of North MK

March 2011 — March 2011

Certificate of tactics in natural conditions summer camp , FON university with ARM and Police Forces of North MK

May 2010 — May 2010

□ Degree in kick boxing - green belt (2006) □ Degree in kick boxing - blue belt (2007), ZA NED DO Academy for Martial Arts

September 2006 — September 2008

Certificate for successful completed English language course , Studiorum School of English Language

September 2004 - September 2005

Сертификат за учество на обука за АНТИДИСКРИМИНАЦИЈА 13-14 октомври Крушево